Guide to the Jesse H. Jones Corporate and Property records, 1836-2008 MS 621
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Property Records, 234181
  - Harris County Additions and Subdivisions, 260963
    - Houston Farms Sub-Division, 261503
      - Lots 63, 65-67; Bulanek Property; 1923, 261505 (Box 149, Folder 34)
      - Lots 65-67, Frank Bobalik; 1924-1941, 261506 (Box 149, Folder 35)
      - Lots 8-10; E. Sonka Loan; 1920-1922, 261507 (Box 149, Folder 36)
      - Lots 55, 60-61; Fakes Loan; 1925-1933, 261508 (Box 149, Folder 37)
      - Peddie Land Company; 1883-1975, 261509 (Box 149, Folder 38-39)
      - Peddie Lands; 1897-1938, 261510 (Box 149, Folder 40-41)
      - Peddie Lands; 1897-1938, 261511 (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lots 22, 25-26; n.d., 261512 (Box 150, Folder 2-3)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lots 29; A-116623, J-417873; 1921-1991, 261513 (Box 150, Folder 4-7)
      - Title Documents; Lot 55; 1922-1990, 261514 (Box 150, Folder 8)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 56; 1922-1991, 261515 (Box 150, Folder 9)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 57; 1921-1991, 261516 (Box 150, Folder 10-11)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 58; 1921-1990, 261517 (Box 150, Folder 12-13)
      - Title Documents; Lot 59; 1925-1991, 261670 (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 60; 1921-1990 (I), 261671 (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 60; 1921-1990 (II), 261672 (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 61; 1921-1990 (I), 261673 (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 61; 1921-1990 (II), 261674 (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 61; 1921-1990 (III), 261675 (Box 151, Folder 6)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 63; 1922-1991, 261676 (Box 151, Folder 7)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 65; 1921-1991 (I), 261677 (Box 151, Folder 8)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 65; 1921-1991 (II), 261678 (Box 151, Folder 9)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 66; 1921-1991 (I), 261679 (Box 151, Folder 10)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 66; 1921-1991 (II), 261680 (Box 151, Folder 11)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 66; 1921-1991 (III), 261681 (Box 151, Folder 12)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 67; 1921-1991 (I), 261682 (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - Chain of Title Reports; Lot 67; 1921-1991 (II), 261683 (Box 152, Folder 2)
      - Assessor's Block Book; 1989-1991, 261684 (Box 152, Folder 3)
      - Peddie Lands; 1918-1990, 261686 (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - Peddie Lands; 1922-1990, 261687 (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - Abstract of Title; 1839,1918-1924, 261691 (Box 152, Folder 6)
      - Abstract of Title; 1916, 261695 (Box 152, Folder 7)
      - Abstract of Title; Part of Lot 1; 1918, 261698 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Houston Heights Addition, 261700
      - Abstract of Title to Lands Belonging to the Houston Land & Irrigation Co.; undated (I), 261699 (Box 152, Folder 9)
      - Block 86; Bolton Property; 1901-1911, 261710 (Box 152, Folder 10)
      - Block 86; Bolton Property; 1901-1927, 261717 (Box 152, Folder 11)
      - Block 86; Bolton Property; Tax Receipts; 1904-1932, 261720 (Box 152, Folder 12)
      - Block 86; Bolton Property; 1913-1917, 261722 (Box 152, Folder 13)
      - Block 92; Lots 19,20,21,22,23,24 to Reagan State Bank; 1926-1956, 261723 (Box 152, Folder 14)
      - Block 93; Lots 38,39,40 William & Annie Schultz; 1953-1954, 261724 (Box 152, Folder 15)
      - Block 104; Lots 19,20; 1903-1911, 261726 (Box 152, Folder 16)
      - Block 138; Abstracts; 1896-1935, 261735 (Box 152, Folder 17)
      - Block 143; Lots 4,5; 1904, 261737 (Box 152, Folder 18)
      - Block 187; Lot 19 Ida G. Powell; 1927-1946, 261738 (Box 152, Folder 19)
      - Block 263; Lots 1,2; 1906, 261739 (Box 152, Folder 20)
      - Block 332; Lots 11,12; 1920, 261740 (Box 152, Folder 21)
    - Houston Street Railway Addition #1, 261741
      - Block 28; Lots 7,8 Construction Contract; 1907-1910, 261742 (Box 152, Folder 22)
    - Hutcheson Addition, 261750
      - Block 4; Lots 4-102; 1912, 261751 (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - Block 4; Lots 4,5,6 Filling Station Main at McGowen; 1919, 261752 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Hyde Park, 261753
      - Block 4; Lots 6-10; 1908, 261754 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Hyde Park Main Addition, 261756
      - Block 17; Lot 13 Gaudet Loan; 1932-1946, 261759 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      - Block 28; Lot 2 Southern Loan & Investment Co. to A. J. McMillian; 1924-1925, 261761 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Irvinton, 261762
      - NSBB; 1891, 261763 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Jarrell Addition, 261764
      - Block 11; Lot 7 Turner Quit Claim; 1951, 261767 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Johnson Home, 261770
      - Block C-1; 1908-1908, 261774 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Kenilworth Grove Addition, 261775
      - Block 62; Lot 1; 1910, 261776 (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - Kirby Main Street Addition, 261777
      - Block 3; Lots 8-10; Block 2; Lots 3-4; 1909-1913, 261781 (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Lancaster Place Addition Extension #2, 261782
      - Block 5; Lot 8 1631 Colquitt; Commerce Co. to Mamie Mason; 1923-1951, 261783 (Box 153, Folder 11)
      - Block 5; Lot 17 Thomas Taylor Property; 1924-1932, 261784 (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Lenox Grove Addition, 261785
      - Block 7; Lot 9 217 Lenox; William S. & Bertita Wilson Loan; 1909-1938, 261786 (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Liberty Heights Addition, 261787
      - Block 22; Lot 7 7128 Market Street; 3rd Subdivision; 1925-1945, 261788 (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Little Addition, 261789
      - Block 29; Lots 3,4; 1910-1911, 261791 (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - Little Dickenson Addition, 261792
      - Block 45; Lot 1; 1959, 261793 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - Little York Subdivision, 261794
      - Lot 69 10 Acres Hilmer Purchase; 1943, 261795 (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - Lockard C & B, 261877
      - Block 14; 1907-1910, 261878 (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - Lockhart, Connor & Barzoria Addition, 261880
      - Block 18; Lots 1,2; 1923-1942, 261883 (Box 153, Folder 19)
    - I. C. Lord Addition
      - Block 2 Lot 1: SL Bishkin Sale, 1927-1944 (Box 153, Folder 20)
    - Lyons Park Avenue Addition and Subdivision, 1927-1941
      - Block 1 Lot 7, Leon + Ethel Banks, 1941 (Box 153, Folder 21)
      - Block 3 Lot 9, Omie S. Brown, 1937 (Box 153, Folder 22)
      - Block 3 Lot 6, 1941 (Box 153, Folder 23)
      - Block 6, 1943 (Box 153, Folder 24)
      - Block 7 Lot 11, 1935 (Box 153, Folder 25)
      - Paving Lyons Ave, 1927-1934 (Box 153, Folder 26)
      - Main Street Properties, Inc. Collateral Security, Various Blocks, 1934-1941 (Box 153, Folder 27)
    - Lyons Avenue Park Addition and Lyons Avenue Park Extension Addition, 1927-1960
      - Abstract, 1941 (Box 153, Folder 28)
      - Block 8, 1945-1949 (Box 153, Folder 29)
      - Various Blocks + Lots, Sales, Loans + Foreclosures, 1927-1953 (Box 153, Folder 30)
      - Various Blocks + Lots, Sales, Loans + Foreclosures, 1927-1953 (Box 153, Folder 31)
      - Various Blocks + Lots, Sales, Loans + Foreclosures, 1927-1953 (Box 153, Folder 32)
      - Various Blocks + Lots, Boundary Dispute, 1927-1960 (Box 153, Folder 33)
      - Various Blocks + Lots, Boundary Dispute, 1927-1960 (Box 153, Folder 34)
    - MacGregor's South End Addition
      - Block 1, 1906-1911 (Box 153, Folder 35)
      - Block 2, 1905-1912 (Box 153, Folder 36)
      - Block 4, 1906 (Box 153, Folder 37)
      - Block 5, 1916 (Box 153, Folder 38)
      - Block 7, 1906-1910 (Box 153, Folder 39)
      - Block 8, 1906-1912 (Box 153, Folder 40)
      - Block 9, 1906-1912 (Box 153, Folder 41)
    - Magnolia Addition
      - Blgd. Lease, Lots 20, 21, 22, 23, 1222 Patterson, 1934-1936 (Box 153, Folder 42)
    - Magnolia Park Addition
      - Block 4 Lot 4, 6708 Capitol Ave. Gertrude Fuselier, 1926-1943 (Box 153, Folder 43)
    - Magnolia Park Sub-Division
      - Block 76 Lots 23-24, Jacinto L. Rodriguez, 1925-1946 (Box 153, Folder 44)
    - Main Street Addition
      - Block 1, 1907 (Box 153, Folder 45)
      - Block 12, 1906-1921 (Box 153, Folder 46)
      - Block 14, 1907-1909 (Box 153, Folder 47)
    - Manchester Subdivision
      - Block 51 Lots 31-32, F.S. Irwin, 1925-1942 (Box 153, Folder 48)
    - Mandell Place Addition
      - Block 7 Lot 9, 1609 Hawthorne, 1925-1943 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Lula B. McCombs and Independent Heights Additions
      - BMC Loan to; Chester McBride, 1925-1944 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Montrose Addition
      - Lots 8, 9, 10, 3617 Montrose, Block 30, 1924-1954 (Box 154, Folder 3)
      - Block 33 Lots 6, 7, 8, 1923-1945 (Box 154, Folder 4)
      - Carroll Lease, Block 33 Lots 6, 7, 8, 3917 Montrose, 1934 (Box 154, Folder 5)
      - Block 37 Lots 8, 10, 11, 12, 14, 4207 Yoakum, Giraud Loan, 1926-1941 (Box 154, Folder 6)
      - Block 42 Lots 11, 12, 13; A.D. Dyess Loan, Yoakum + W. Alabama, 1921-1926 (Box 154, Folder 7)
      - Block 43, 1915 (Box 154, Folder 8)
      - Block 46- Various Lots, 1912-1978 (Box 154, Folder 9)
      - Block 46- Various Lots, 1912-1978 (Box 154, Folder 10)
      - Block 46- Various Lots, Cancelled Notes, 1931-1941 (Box 154, Folder 11)
      - Block 46, 1959 (Box 154, Folder 12)
      - Block 57 Lots 2, 3, 4, 6, 14; W.L. Moore, 1922-1939 (Box 154, Folder 13)
      - Block 57 Lot 14, TC Dunn Loan, 1940-1943 (Box 154, Folder 14)
      - Lease Proposal, 1969 (Box 154, Folder 15)
      - Abstracts of Title, 1917; 1928; 1929 (Box 154, Folder 16)
      - Abstracts of Title, 1919-1927 (Box 154, Folder 17)
      - Abstracts of Title, 1923-1952 (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - Montrose Annex Addition
      - BMC Loan to: Bates Wilson; Block 78 Lot 7, 1923-1927 (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - Nassau Bay Sub-Division
      - BMC Loan to: B.J. Roberts, 1971-1971 (Box 154, Folder 20)
    - Nobel Addition
      - Block 24, 1904-1908 (Box 154, Folder 21)
      - Block 25 Lots 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 1905-1924 (Box 154, Folder 22)
      - Block 25 Lots 5-9, 1925-1946 (Box 154, Folder 23)
      - Block 25 Lots 5, 6; 2000-06 N. San Jacinto, 1935 (Box 154, Folder 24)
      - Block 25 Lots 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9; Block 28 Lots 3, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 1932-1953 (Box 154, Folder 25)
      - Block 28, 1914-1926 (Box 154, Folder 26)
      - Blocks 43, 44, 45, 1892-1912 (Box 154, Folder 27)
      - Block 44, 1923 (Box 154, Folder 28)
      - Block 45 Lots 5, 6, 1911-1915 (Box 154, Folder 29)
      - Block 45 Lots 5, 6; Mrs. Ray Rudy, 1924-1950 (Box 154, Folder 30)
      - Block 75, 1909 (Box 154, Folder 31)
      - Louisa Jones Notes, 1914-1921 (Box 154, Folder 32)
    - Norhill Addition
      - BMC Loan to: Lydia J. Baker, Block 8 Lot 12, 1127 Omar, 1923-1943 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - H.A. Paine Addition
      - Block 6 Lot 3, 2203 Scott St. Cordelia Allen Loan ( AKA Aunt Miranon), 1934-1952 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Parker Smith Addition
      - Block 16 Lot 1, Clay Loan, 1925-1948 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Parkwood Addition
      - Various Documents, 1940-1947 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Pershing Place Addition and Lindel Park Addition # 5
      - Block 2 Lot 2; Block 27 Lot 22, 1949-1960 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Post Oak Village Addition
      - BMC Loans to: Cambridge Corp. Various Sections, 1956-1960 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Ridgewood Addition
      - Block 62, 1926-1930 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - River Oaks Addition
      - BMC Loan to: E.H. Preston, Block 83 Lot 14, 3741 Del Monte, 1965-1969 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Riverside Extension Addition
      - Block 4 Lots 6+7, 2816 Southmore Blvd, R.D. Ernst, 1928-1943 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Riverside Terrace Addition
      - Block 2 Lot 20, 2115 Arbor St., 1927-1943 (Box 155, Folder 10)
      - Loan- Commerce Co. to James T. Bellany, Sec. 21 Block 89 Lot 3, 1946-1948 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Rosedale Addition
      - Lots 21-22, Welch House, 1105-07 Willard Ave., 1923-1936 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Rosewood Addition
      - Block 10 Lot 8, 1504 Rosewood, Frances P. Forney, 1928-1942 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Rossmoyne Addition
      - Block 2 Lots 23, 4307 Mt. Vernon, 1923-1936 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Royal Oaks Addition
      - Block 4 Lot 10, Bellamy Sale, 1959 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - San Jose Addition
      - Block 1 + 2, Various Loans, 1927-1945 (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Seligmann Addition
      - Maurice Hirsch Property, 1929-1952 (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Settegast-Upham Addition
      - Various Documents, 1911-1915 (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - Shannon Addition
      - Block 1 Lot 5, 140 N. Milby, George Loan, 1935-1944 (Box 155, Folder 19)
    - Southampton Place Addition
      - Block 20 Lot 8, Thornton Loan, 1927-1947 (Box 155, Folder 20)
      - Block 21 Lot 3, 2226 Quenby, GJ Sullivan Loan, 1929-1953 (Box 155, Folder 21)
      - Vestry + Wardens of Christ Church, Block 33 Lot 4, 1818 Sunset Blvd, 1934 (Box 155, Folder 22)
    - Southdale Addition
      - Block 20 + Willa Bord, 1938-1939 (Box 155, Folder 23)
    - South End Villa Addition
      - Various Documents, 1908-1909 (Box 155, Folder 24)
      - McClain Lease, Block 7 Lot 9, 4917 Louisiana St., 1932 (Box 155, Folder 25)
    - Southmore Addition
      - St. Paul's Methodist Church, 1950-1957 (Box 155, Folder 27)
      - Various Documents, 1909-1936 (Box 155, Folder 26)
    - Southside Place Addition
      - Block 2 Lot 19, 1928-1948 (Box 155, Folder 28)
      - Block 2 Lot 20, Young Loan, 1926-1943 (Box 155, Folder 29)
      - Simonton Lease, Block 2 Lot 20, 6554 Auden St., 1933 (Box 155, Folder 30)
      - BMC Loan to: Addie H. Wilson, Block 12 Lot 7, 3760 Ingold, 1946-1966 (Box 155, Folder 31)
      - Abstract of Title, 1924 (Box 155, Folder 32)
      - Abstracts of Title, 1924-1926 (Box 155, Folder 33)
      - Abstracts of Title, 1928-1955 (Box 155, Folder 34)
    - M.A. Stevens Addition
      - Various Documents, 1913-1927 (Box 155, Folder 35)
      - Lots 8, 9, 20, 1920 (Box 155, Folder 36)
    - Stratford Addition
      - Various Documents, 1928-1929 (Box 155, Folder 37)
    - Sunset Heights Addition
      - Block 2 Lots 16 + 17, 1925-1932 (Box 156, Folder 1)
      - Block 2 Lots 16 + 17, 1932-1945 (Box 156, Folder 2)
      - Block 6 Lots 8 + 9, 701 E. 29th, Larry + Dora Berker, 1927-1943 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Swiney Home Reserve
      - Swiney Home Reserve (n.s.b.b.), 1914-1916 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Turner Addition
      - Block 15- Hedgecroft Clininc, 5120 Montrose, 1948-1953 (Box 156, Folder 5)
      - Abstracts of Title to Block 15, 1919-1944 (Box 156, Folder 6)
      - Abstract of Title to Block 15, 1919-1948 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - University Place Addition
      - Blocks 4, 5, 6, 7, Main St. AT Bellaire Blvd. W.C. Munn Note, 1931-1940 (Box 156, Folder 8)
      - Blocks 4, 5, 6, 7, Main St. AT Bellaire Blvd. W.C. Munn Note, 1931-1940 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Various Additions
      - So. Loan + Invco Loan to: A.A. Moore, 1923-1926 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Washington Terrace Addition
      - Block 1 Lot 10- 2112 E. Alabama, Stein Loan, 1941-1950 (Box 156, Folder 11)
      - BMC Loan to: Clarence Washington, Jr. Block 11 Lot 12, 2519 Barbee St., 1934-1963 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Westmoreland Addition
      - Abstract of Title, 1925-1951 (Box 156, Folder 13)
      - Block 1 Lot 11, 1907-1913 (Box 156, Folder 14)
      - Block 1 Lot 11, 1907-1913 (Box 156, Folder 14)
      - Block 1 Lot 21, 1907-1908 (Box 156, Folder 15)
      - Block 1 Lots 23, 24, 1907-1920 (Box 156, Folder 16)
      - Block 1 Lots 27, 28, 1906 (Box 156, Folder 17)
      - Block 2 Lots 15, 16, 1905 (Box 156, Folder 18)
      - Block 3 Lots 3, 4, 1906-1911 (Box 156, Folder 19)
      - Block 3 Lots 1/2 of 7, 8, 1905-1909 (Box 156, Folder 20)
      - Block 4 Lots 1, 2, 1906-1909 (Box 156, Folder 21)
      - Block 4 Lots 8, 9, 1905-1911 (Box 156, Folder 22)
      - Block 5 Lots 1/2 of 4, 5, 1907 (Box 156, Folder 23)
      - Block 6 Lots Pt. 4 + 6, 5, 1906-1911 (Box 156, Folder 24)
      - Block 6 Lots 14, 1/2 of 15, 1906 (Box 156, Folder 25)
      - Block 6 Lot 18, Pt. of 19, 1909 (Box 156, Folder 26)
      - SIMG Reservation, Block 7, 1906-1914 (Box 156, Folder 27)
      - Block 7, 1906-1919 (Box 156, Folder 28)
      - Block 8 Lots 1/2 11, 12, 1906-1919 (Box 156, Folder 29)
      - Block 8 Lot 13, 1906-1914 (Box 156, Folder 30)
      - Block 8 Lot 14, 1906-1914 (Box 156, Folder 31)
      - Block 8 Lot 15, 1906-1914 (Box 156, Folder 32)
      - Block 9 Lots 1/2 of 7, 8, 1906-1910 (Box 156, Folder 33)
      - Block 9 Lot 9, 1906 (Box 156, Folder 34)
      - Block 9 Lot 10, 1908 (Box 156, Folder 35)
      - Block 9 Lots 13, 1/4 of 14, 1906 (Box 156, Folder 36)
      - Block 10 Lots 8, 9, 1907 (Box 156, Folder 37)
      - O.T. Webb House, Forest McNeir- Builder, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 38)
    - Westmoreland Farms Sub-Division
      - AA Sterling Loan, Block 25, 1924-1937 (Box 156, Folder 39)
      - Land Leases, Sanderson, House, Twist, Vince Surveys, Block 25, 1935-1939 (Box 156, Folder 40)
    - Weston Addition
      - Various Documents, 1910-1912 (Box 156, Folder 41)
    - Westover Addition
      - Lot 22- 1105 Drew, Gayle Loan, 1931-1941 (Box 156, Folder 42)
    - West University Place Addition
      - Block 3 Lot 3, Carl J. Shikutt, 1927-1948 (Box 156, Folder 43)
      - Block 5 Lots 11, 12, 1956-1962 (Box 156, Folder 44)
    - Whitney Place Addition
      - Block 18 Lot 19, C.C. + Allie Bullard, 1937-1944 (Box 156, Folder 45)
    - Wilson's Addition
      - Various Documents, 1910-1917 (Box 156, Folder 46)
    - Winlow Place Addition
      - Block 3 Lot 12, Mt + Bertha Schmidt, 1925-1945 (Box 156, Folder 47)
    - Woodland Heights Addition
      - Burton Lease, Block 23 Lots 4, 5, 514 Euclid St., 1938 (Box 156, Folder 48)
    - Woodland Terrace Addition
      - Block 12 Lot 13, 807 Teetshorn, Turner Loan, 1926-1943 (Box 156, Folder 49)
    - Woodleigh Addition
      - Block 10 Lot 23, 1924-1944 (Box 156, Folder 50)
      - Block 10 Lot 23, Goedicke Loan, 1924-1948 (Box 156, Folder 51)
      - Holland Lease, Block 10 Lot 23, 3913 Dallas Ave, 1931 (Box 156, Folder 52)
      - Block 4 Lot 23, 915 Omar, 1923-1941 (Box 156, Folder 53)
      - Block 4 Lot 10, 938-40 Merrill, W.S. Scott, 1924-1945 (Box 156, Folder 54)
    - Woodson Place Addition
      - Block 4 Lot 4, 1943 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Young Men's Addition
      - Various Documents, 1892-1915 (Box 157, Folder 2)
      - Lot 2, Butler Tract, 1907-1909 (Box 157, Folder 3)
      - Block 14, Lots 9-12, 1901-1937 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Various Additions
      - Anderson Property, 1905 (Box 157, Folder 5)
      - Colton Property, 1911 (Box 157, Folder 6)
      - Garrow vs Taylor, Defendant - J. Wade Cox, 1908 (Box 157, Folder 7)
      - The Houston Post, 1954-1956 (Box 157, Folder 8)
      - BMC Bonds, 1923-1929 (Box 157, Folder 9)
      - Toll Bridge, 1967 (Box 157, Folder 10)
      - La Porte, 1902-1916 (Box 157, Folder 11)
      - La Porte, Block 180 Lots 1-32, H.C. Leftwich, 1941-1946 (Box 157, Folder 12)
      - National Maritime Union Lease, 1519 75th St., 1937-1941 (Box 157, Folder 13)
      - Niday Property, 1908 (Box 157, Folder 14)
      - Landleases- Pasadena, 1942-1945 (Box 157, Folder 15)
      - Seabrook, Texas, Block 171 Lots 1, 2, 3, 1919 (Box 157, Folder 16)
      - 1220 Homer Dr. Thomas Loan, 1956-1966 (Box 157, Folder 17)
      - 1232 Peden Ave Lease, 1925 (Box 157, Folder 18)
      - 1631 Colquitt, 1928 (Box 157, Folder 19)
  - Harris County: South Side of Buffalo Bayou (SSBB)
    - Block 20
      - Various Documents, 1909-1915 (Box 157, Folder 20)
    - Block 33
      - Lot 1, Kiam Building, 1907-1917 (Box 157, Folder 21)
      - Lot 5, Sterne Building, 1911-1937 (Box 157, Folder 22)
      - Stern Building, federal Cloth Stores, 1925-137 (Box 157, Folder 23)
      - Misc. Leases, 1925-1937 (Box 157, Folder 24)
    - Block 34
      - Deuster Building, 311 Travis, 1925 (Box 157, Folder 25)
    - Block 42
      - Lots 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 11, 12, Houston Chronicle Publishing Co., 1973 (Box 157, Folder 26)
    - Block 44
      - Jones vs Sakowitz, Christie Bldg. Corp., 1922-1941 (Box 157, Folder 27)
      - Jones vs Sakowitz, Christie Bldg. Corp., 1922-1941 (Box 157, Folder 28)
      - Jones vs Sakowitz, Christie Bldg. Corp., 1922-1941 (Box 157, Folder 29)
      - Jones vs Sakowitz, Christie Bldg. Corp., 1922-1941 (Box 157, Folder 30)
      - Jones vs Sakowitz, Christie Bldg. Corp., 1922-1941 (Box 157, Folder 31)
    - Block 45
      - Paul Bldg. Property, Sheppard Est. Lease to Mason Building Co., 1917 (Box 157, Folder 32)
    - Block 46
      - Lots 3, 4, 5, Lane Building, 1921-1925 (Box 157, Folder 33)
    - Block 51
      - 1502-1516 Texas Ave. Hotel Victor + Storeroom Leases, 1916-1924 (Box 157, Folder 34)
      - Wilson Property, 1910-1913 (Box 157, Folder 35)
      - Main + Congress Realty Co. (Warehouse + Cold Storage), 1912-1915 (Box 157, Folder 36)
      - Receipts + Maps, 1914-1926 (Box 157, Folder 37)
      - Houston Terminal WHSE + Cold Storage, 1926-1928 (Box 157, Folder 38)
      - Houston Terminal WHSE + Cold Storage Estimates, 1927 (Box 157, Folder 39)
      - Baker Warehouse Building, 700 N. San Jacinto St., 1927 (Box 157, Folder 40)
      - Houston Terminal WHSE + Cold Storage Financing, 1929-1936 (Box 157, Folder 41)
      - Houston Terminal WHSE + Cold Storage Financing, 1938-1965 (Box 157, Folder 42)
      - Houston Terminal WHSE + Cold Storage to So. Texas Jr. College, 1946-1972 (Box 157, Folder 43)
      - Houston Terminal WHSE + Cold Storage to So. Texas Jr. College, 1946-1972 (Box 157, Folder 44)
      - Houston Terminal WHSE + Cold Storage to So. Texas Jr. College, 1946-1972 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Block 55
      - Lots 6, 7, 8, All Right, Inc. Garage Loan, 1950-1952 (Box 158, Folder 2)
      - Lots 6, 7, 8, All Right, Inc. Garage Loan, 1950-1952 (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - Refunding Certificates, 1900 (Box 158, Folder 4)
      - Dienstag Bldg., 1909-1987 (Box 158, Folder 5)
      - Dienstag Bldg., 1909-1987 (Box 158, Folder 6)
      - Dienstag Bldg., 1909-1987 (Box 158, Folder 7)
      - Dienstag Bldg., 1909-1987 (Box 158, Folder 8)
      - Lots 9 + 10, M.E. Foster Lease to: Spoon + McGuire, 1116 Prairie, 1916 (Box 158, Folder 9)
      - Lots 9 + 10, Dienstag Building Leases, 1920-1925 (Box 158, Folder 10)
      - Lots 9 + 10, Dienstag Building Leases, 1927-1940 (Box 158, Folder 11)
      - Dienstag Bldg. Collapse, 6/20/1951, 1948-1952 (Box 158, Folder 12)
      - Lots 9 + 10- Lease Payments, 1951-1959 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - Block 57
      - Rice Hotel, Stationary (From HPL), n.d. (Box 158, Folder 14)
      - Rice Hotel, Rice Institute Loan to Houston Hotel Association, 1912-1914 (Box 158, Folder 15)
      - Rice Hotel, Articles of Inc., 1911 (Box 158, Folder 16)
      - Rice Hotel, Assignment of Leasehold Insterest, 1923 (Box 158, Folder 17)
      - Rice Hotel, Houston Hotel Co., 1906 (Box 158, Folder 18)
      - Rice Hotel, Bond Issue, 1907 (Box 158, Folder 19)
      - Rice Hotel, Houston Hotel Association, 1910-1914 (Box 158, Folder 20)
      - Rice Hotel, Subc-Contractors, 1911-1912 (Box 158, Folder 21)
      - Rice Hotel, Southwestern Telegraph and Telephone Co., 1912 (Box 158, Folder 22)
      - Rice Hotel, J.M. West Rice Hotel Co. Stock, 1912 (Box 158, Folder 23)
      - Rice Hotel, Peden Iron and Steel, 1912-1913 (Box 158, Folder 24)
      - Rice Hotel, Westlake Construction Co. Correspondence, 1912-1914 (Box 158, Folder 25)
      - Rice Hotel, Bathroom Fixtures, 1912-1913 (Box 158, Folder 26)
      - Rice Hotel, Otis Elevator Co., 1912-1916 (Box 158, Folder 27)
      - Rice Hotel, Releases, 1912-1926 (Box 158, Folder 28)
      - Rice Hotel, Bar Supplies, 1913 (Box 158, Folder 29)
      - Rice Hotel, Keithly Co. Bond, 1913 (Box 158, Folder 30)
      - Rice Hotel, Cancelled Notes, 1913-1919 (Box 158, Folder 31)
      - Rice Hotel, Claims, 1912-1914 (Box 158, Folder 32)
      - Rice Hotel, H.J. Schmidt vs Randolph Paint Co., 1913-1914 (Box 158, Folder 33)